- Mm.
- Morning.
Morning.
You know what today is, right?
- Mm.
- RDO.
Oh, this is what a day off feels like.
You want some coffee?
I want you,
and then I want coffee,
and then I want waffles,
and then I want to go to the range
and try out those new .44 mags.
I love all that.
I love you.
Um, just one sec.
I'll be right back.
Hey, I forgot that
I was gonna take my car in,
and I just talked to them,
and they can still take me,
and so I'm gonna go
before they get busy.
Really?
One day off, you know?
Hailey.
I just feel like I should get it done,
but everything's fine.
Um, I'm sorry, but I... um,
stay here. I'll be right back.
And yeah, just hang out here,
and I'll be back in a little bit.
Possible mental illness involved.
Supervisor advised. You on scene?
Copy, car's rolling.
2124, got a wellness check.
3839 North Racine.
Caller states multiple members
of the Clarton family are gone.
Possible missing persons.
5021 Henry, hold me down
on that missing persons.
Copy, 5021 Henry.
Morning.
Detective Hailey Upton.
Morning. Your with Intelligence, yeah?
Dispatch detailed you?
- No, I just picked it up.
- Ah, okay.
There's probably not much for you here.
Next door neighbor, Jessica Hartley...
She's right over there... called it in.
Hasn't seen her neighbors in a few days.
The Clarton family.
Dad Ray, wife Helen,
and their kid, Becca.
She's 12.
- Signs of forced entry?
- Nah.
Sarge gave me the green light
to enter in a wellness check.
Front door was unlocked.
No signs of foul play.
Everything seems fine inside.
Jessica?
Hi, I'm Detective Hailey Upton.
When was the last time
you saw your neighbors?
A few days. Uh...
Goose, what day did we see them?
Before dance.
Right, so it would've been Tuesday.
- And this isn't like them?
- No.
I mean, I'm probably overreacting,
nosy next door neighbor.
It's just, they don't ever go anywhere,
and I had just talked to Helen.
I'm sorry.
I'm probably wasting your time.
It's just something felt off.
No. No time wasted.
We'll be right back.
You're the only one that's been inside?
Yeah.
Said they lived here for a while?
They're renting it.
Been here six months.
Smell that?
Place has been bleached recently.
Spring cleaning?
Garbage was taken out.
Bag wasn't replaced.
Man, I wish my daughter was this neat.
I can't even get her
to put her dirty clothes
in the laundry basket.
Can you get over here
and help me move this bed?
Towards you. Ready?
Yeah.
5021 Henry, I'm at the missing persons.
I need a crime lab rolled here ASAP.
Copy that, 5021 Henry.
Crime lab en route.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Hey.
I had ones like those when I was a kid.
Swallows.
So you didn't make it to the shop, huh?
Uh, no. Um...
No, I didn't.
Team's just arriving.
Clarton home, husband Ray,
wife Helen, daughter Becca.
Talked to the rest of the block.
No one's seen them in at least two days.
And that's odd?
To our neighbor, Jessica, yeah.
They were homebodies.
She said she just spoke with Helen
to get together the next day.
She called both their cells.
No one's answering.
Checked the phones,
and they're shut off.
And her car's in the garage.
There's cardboard boxes upstairs.
Empty suitcases.
They might've been packing.
Hey. Got something weird.
So I ran the name and social
the landlord gave me, Ray Clarton.
Problem is, Ray Clarton died
four years ago.
- He's using a false name?
- Yeah, on everything.
Utilities for the house,
credit card, car,
- all registered to a dead man.
- Okay, what about the wife?
She's not on paper anywhere,
and I got no hits on a Helen Clarton
in Chicago matching her descriptors.
The little girl, Becca, she's 12.
- She must be in school.
- She's not.
Not registered with CPS.
Not in a private school.
Ran missing persons too,
and I got nothing.
So dig into the name, Ray Clarton,
and see who had access
to steal his identity.
Let's do a full forensics search.
Let's find out who the hell
this family really is.
What the hell happened in this house?
Something happened to them,
and you think
they were using fake names?
We know they were.
That doesn't make any sense.
They're a perfectly normal family.
Things often look normal,
but can't really know a family
unless they let you.
Do you know where Ray and Helen work?
Uh, Helen stays home.
I don't know about Ray.
All right, what about
where they're from?
Hometown?
I don't, um... I don't know.
Annie, were you friends with Becca?
No. She doesn't go to my school.
Becca seemed shy.
She keeps to herself.
Okay.
Anything you can tell us
about them at all,
really anything would help.
I don't know. I just...
Sometimes I do wonder about
how old-fashioned they are.
What do you mean?
Uh, it's just, Ray runs the house,
really runs it.
It doesn't seem like the girls
are independent.
Does he hurt them?
What? No.
Oh, God no.
I'm sure he doesn't hurt them.
I'm sure it's not that.
There's something wrong
with this family.
This little girl, Becca...
- All right, what do we got?
- Forensics came back.
Blood in the master is two days old
and belongs to a female.
DNA doesn't match anything on file,
but the tech said as long as
the blood came from an adult,
the amount of blood is not enough
to positively indicate a death.
Fingerprints off all the men's shoes
in the Clarton house
ID'd Ray's real name.
Meet Ray Aimes.
We've got a hell of a sheet.
Lived in 14 different states
the past 20 years,
multiple fraud investigations,
two domestics when he was younger.
Looks like he mostly deals
in Ponzi and pyramid schemes.
He's a grifter.
He's an old school conman.
He gets in close with people,
manipulates the hell out
of them, robs them blind,
and then he skips town.
What about the girls, Helen and Becca?
Their prints weren't in the system.
Ray's not legally married,
but the DNA found off
of the toothbrush in the home
confirms that Becca
is Ray and Helen's child.
And she's never been enrolled in school?
I checked everywhere that Ray lived.
She never been enrolled in school.
She never even been to a doctor.
Nothing.
I'm guessing there's abuse
in this family.
Physical, emotional.
- So you're thinking domestic?
- Makes sense.
We have a history of domestic assault.
He beats Helen too bad one day,
throws them both in the car,
takes off before he was planning to.
Ladies and gentlemen, we got a pop.
Ray Clarton's debit card
was used at an ATM
downtown yesterday
right after they went missing.
Roll on it.
All right, so your boy
and his daughter got there
at 9:15 a.m. Already called up the bank.
Ray withdrew the entirety
of his checking account.
$1,500.
Wait, we got a PO.
Is this kid gonna ask for help?
No, she's not.
She looks scared.
- Do you have more cameras?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, who the hell is that?
It's not a domestic. Somebody took them.
All right, who is this man?
Someone from Ray's past
come back to haunt him?
Maybe Ray conned the wrong guy,
end up over his head?
I've got no large deposits
on Ray's financials.
Nothing pops on the video.
Clothes are generic.
- Can't even make out Ray's.
- It really doesn't help
we know next to nothing
about this family.
Yeah, I reinterviewed
the neighbors on the block.
Nobody knew where they worked,
where they were from,
their family, nothing.
We have zero details on them.
Ray and Helen are good.
Yeah, but you learn how to be that way.
To shut people out, be invisible,
you learn it.
Becca's only 12 years old.
Maybe she hasn't learned
how to do that just yet.
We've been through
every inch of this place.
I don't know what else we're gonna find.
Anything. Anything that'll tell us
who they really are,
who might've taken them.
Jay, listen, um, about this morning.
I'm sorry.
I just got overwhelmed.
I kinda figured that when you
ran out of your apartment
and caught a case.
Uh, I just panicked.
It's not that I don't care
about you, or that I...
Hailey, there's a little girl
that's missing right now,
so we can do this later.
Really.
Kay.
Hey.
My partner's downstairs
with your mom and dad.
They said it was okay if you
and I chat a little bit.
- That all right with you?
- Uh-huh.
All right.
I like your room.
Hey, Becca's got the same ones.
You guys are good friends, huh?
Not really.
Hmm.
Becca's room does not look like this.
Her whole house really.
I've been a cop for 12 years,
and I think I can feel it now.
You know, when something feels wrong?
Becca's house is like that, right?
I don't know. I've never been there.
Hmm.
Is it okay if I sit?
Sure.
I had a house like that
when I was a kid.
Something was wrong.
I didn't tell anybody,
but I did have a best friend.
She lived down the street from me,
and even though I never told her
a word of it, she knew.
She knew something wrong,
and she would keep
her window unlocked for me,
so I could come inside
if I needed a place to hide.
Is that what the flashlights are for?
So you can go downstairs
and let Becca in?
Annie, you're a good friend.
You love her.
Sometimes when you love somebody
you have to tell the truth,
even if it feels like
you're betraying something.
Do you know what happened
to the Clartons?
Okay.
I don't understand what's going on.
You've hardly told us anything.
- Should we be calling a lawyer?
- No, no, no.
We're only here so it's on
film, and it's recorded.
Okay?
Now tell me the whole thing again.
You and Becca are friends.
Best friends.
- But we have to hide it.
- What?
Why, Annie?
Because the Clartons are scary.
Becca's scared of her parents.
Her dad doesn't let her go to school.
Doesn't let her have friends.
He hurts them.
They used flashlights.
Anytime that Becca wanted to see Annie,
she'd shine a flashlight
through Annie's window.
Annie would wake up,
she'd go downstairs,
unlock the door,
and Becca would come over.
You're kidding me.
Two nights ago, the night
that the Clartons disappeared,
Becca shined a light
through Annie's window.
I saw a man.
He was walking through their house.
Did she get a good look at him?
No, he disappeared through the house.
So I went to the back door.
The man was leading Becca
and her parents outside.
- Mrs. Clarton looked hurt.
- Jesus.
Oh, Annie, why wouldn't
you say something?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay, it's okay, Annie.
We're learning it now. Just keep going.
He put them in a car.
Good, that's good. What kind of car?
A station wagon.
One of those old ones.
He drove away with them.
We don't have a station wagon
on PODs outside that ATM.
Yeah, but we do have a witness
that puts a station wagon
outside the Clarton's house.
I mean, it left and went somewhere.
So get everything going
in a five mile radius.
It's a Mercury. It's a Mercury.
We showed Annie a dozen models,
and she pointed right to it.
I got one.
Real close to the Clartons' house,
11:23 p.m.,
heading northbound on Western.
Yep, I got him again.
11:29, Western and Franklin.
Headed on 66.
And those plates are hot.
They're stolen.
That's him.
Get those plates out on an all-call.
Five minutes later,
he's still going west on 66.
Just keep following.
See where he leads us.
We get the station wagon
pulling in here,
and then we lose him.
Well, he probably ditched
the car and swapped it.
All right, let's fan out.
- Jay.
- What do you got?
They're the same sheets.
They're the same sheets from the house.
Okay.
Hold on.
Oh, my God.
Her mouth.
Looks like she doesn't have any teeth.
- Or fingerprints.
- Yeah.
Whoever killed her knew
what they were doing.
No way we're gonna get an ID off of her.
The tech search and the banks
haven't found anything.
We've got zero evidence.
This looks like an organized crime kill.
Yeah, well, whoever did it,
they killed her here,
and burned her hands,
pulled her teeth out.
Hopefully in that order.
The offender drove directly
from the Clartons' home
to this location.
He had Becca and Ray in the car
when he killed Helen.
He did that to her body
in front of her little kid.
Why?
$1,500 out of Ray's bank account?
Hey, we got lucky.
Security camera caught a man
in frame for a moment.
There's no wagon or family,
but I think it's the offender.
Might be enough for facial rec.
Yo, Sarge, we got ID.
- Huh.
- Name's Alejandro Hermanez.
His height and weight
matched the ATM video.
- Priors?
- Nothing official.
The FBI, they've been investigating him.
They like him as a for-hire enforcer.
- Uh-huh.
- He works in extortion
and cleanup for organized crime outlets,
most recently the Albanian syndicate.
So Ray upgraded.
Decided to con the big men.
That takes stones.
Well, con is short for confidence.
This time it's short for stupid.
It was definitely stupid.
Last time Hermanez got investigated,
it was for a stash house theft.
Uh-huh.
Somebody skimmed money
and dope off the top,
and Alejandro put him in the ground.
And we found two pro-grade
traps behind a false wall
in a cabinet downstairs.
Let me guess. Both empty.
Yeah, no signs of drug residue,
- so it must've been cash.
- Fits.
These guys love to bury
cash houses in plain sight.
You get a normal looking family
with kids,
safe neighborhood,
safe block, safe money.
So we're thinking Ray was dumb enough
to steal from the Albanians,
skim off the top?
Old habits die hard.
Ray stolen from every person
he's ever met.
Guy manipulates,
controls even his own family.
He probably thought he could skip town
before they caught on.
I mean, it explains why
Hermanez had to abduct him.
He went to the house, kills Helen
to convince Ray to give up that money.
- Mm.
- Right.
But there's no way it was only $1,500.
I mean, those traps
can hide millions in cash.
Hmm.
So if there's still cash out there,
Becca and Ray are still alive.
Hermanez is a pro.
He won't kill them till
he gets all the cash back.
It's possible.
No, not just possible. It's who Ray is.
He would take everything he could.
All right, so where the hell
is Hermanez now?
I don't know have any LKAs,
and the FBI's got zero.
I might have something.
Hermanez has a car.
It's registered to a bogus address,
but he got two tickets
in the last two months,
three blocks from the bathhouse
that Vice ID'd.
It's a brothel.
Okay, so our guy's got a vice.
Maybe somebody there knows
where he hangs his hat.
All right, so you two move on it.
Get an ASA on board.
If we find this guy,
I wanna know we're solid.
Get you all set...
It's this one.
Chicago PD.
Jesus. What the...
You get up, get out.
I'm not touching you
without your clothes on. Let's go.
You're not going anywhere. Back up.
Here.
- The hell is going on?
- You Zara?
We're looking for Alejandro Hermanez.
We're told he's one of your regulars.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, we're not gonna do that.
He kidnapped a 12-year-old girl.
- He's gonna kill her.
- What?
I'm assuming that you know
what he really is.
So let's not pretend
that you weren't once 12,
and that you don't care
about a little kid.
Do you know where he lives?
You ever pay him a private visit,
leave the bosses out of their cut?
Where does he live, Zara?
Or I will happily arrest you
and let the owners of this place know
you're the reason
we're shutting it down.
What do you think
they're gonna do to you then?
Where?
Hegewisch.
He lives outside Hegewisch.
All right, this is the address.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's a trailer.
Sarge, we're at Alejandro's place.
Jay, there's a shed. They're in there.
Sarge, there's a shed on the property.
It's got a padlock on it.
Copy that. Hold eyes on it.
There he is.
Sarge, we got eyes on Hermanez.
He's got a gun on him.
We have every reason to believe
she's in there right now.
I hear you, but wait for backup.
We're on with the ASA. Hold an anchor.
He's walking towards the shed.
We need to move.
Hailey.
Hailey!
Hands behind your back!
Chicago PD. Do not fight me.
- Hailey, you good?
- I'm good.
- You good?
- I'm good! Get on your knees.
- What the hell's going on?
- The shed's clear.
- You got him?
- Yeah, here.
Don't move. Hailey, Hailey!
Hey, what's she doing?
You can't just go into my home!
Shut up, shut up. Come here.
Becca?
So are we no longer listening
to direct orders?
Becca could've been in that shed.
You didn't have
an arrest warrant in hand.
You didn't even have a search warrant.
Sarge, Hermanez had a gun
in plain sight,
so if they had been in there...
All right, get the little girl,
Annie, back in here.
Get her to confirm Hermanez
in a six-pack.
And if we hadn't seen the gun?
I would've moved anyway.
She could've been in that shed.
We'll get it backstopped by an ASA.
It's exigent circumstances. She's a kid.
I just need you to look at these photos
and tell me if you recognize
the man that you saw
the night Becca disappeared, okay?
Is Becca gonna be okay?
I don't know for sure,
but we're doing absolutely everything
in our power to find her.
I'm sorry. I don't know who it was.
Okay.
Tell you what, we're gonna
do it one more time,
and this time,
I want you to look really slowly, okay?
Him.
It was him. I saw him.
Great.
I mean, do you understand? Hmm?
Let me run it down for you.
We have an eye witness
that confirms you were in
the Clartons' house.
We have you on toll cams
in the station wagon.
We have you at the underpass.
We have your DNA on Helen.
We got you locked in.
You gonna die in the cage.
So there's no point
in not talking to us.
Where are Becca and Ray?
It doesn't really matter
what you say to me,
'cause I can whisper to them
that you sang
and make sure you end up in a cell block
where they can reach you,
do what they want.
We don't care about Ray.
In case you hadn't figured it out,
his name's not even Ray Clarton.
He's a low-ranked conman
who beats his wife and kid.
What we care about is the kid.
You tell us where we can find her,
we're gonna put you down
as a cooperating defendant.
Good cell block, prison you choose,
minimum sentence.
Kid doesn't deserve to be
punished for her dad's sins.
So you get a deal.
I don't know who these people are.
I don't know why you entered my home.
I'm very sorry.
They're alive. We can break him.
Yeah, he's messing with us.
'Cause he knows we don't have enough.
All right, what else do we have?
Phone's clean. Nothing on cams.
His car's GPS shows movement
earlier this morning.
Uh-huh.
Hermanez drove to a PO box
in Humboldt Park.
I confirmed with the staff
that Ray owns a PO box there.
Hermanez accessed the box.
He left with that bag.
Two blocks later, it looks like
he made a physical exchange.
So they got their money back.
Ray told Hermanez
where he was hiding it.
All right, do we have
any other leverage?
His financials are pretty clean,
but he does make one deposit each month
- to a long-term care facility.
- Uh-huh.
- Other than that, I don't have any...
- We can use that.
Hermanez is probably paying for family.
We know he doesn't have any
documented family in the U.S.,
so they must be illegal.
So we confirm their noncitizenship,
and we threaten him with ICE.
All right, there's no
guarantee he'll talk for that,
and we can't threaten him unless we know
who it is he's paying for,
ID their citizenship.
So we ID them.
Well, the problem is, that's illegal.
We can't contact ICE.
Can't even ask about citizenship.
You can as a private citizen.
It's still illegal.
I think you know that.
Okay, but it's also all we got.
This is a little girl.
She hasn't been protected
a day in her life.
Doesn't know that she can be,
that she should be.
And if there's a chance that
she could still be alive,
then we protect her.
We will.
Just not that way.
Sarge, it could work,
and we've crossed worse lines before.
Did you not hear me say no?
All right, look.
This is simple.
Ray and Becca are somewhere.
Wherever that is,
there's gonna be
a clear link to Hermanez.
So find it now.
Hey, Hailey.
What's going on?
Come on, you're not going there
anyway, so just stop.
No one's gonna even know I went.
Yeah, what are you gonna do
with the information?
How's no one gonna know
when you use it in the interview room?
I'll figure that part out
if there's anything usable.
What is going on?
- There's a little kid missing.
- I know that.
What's going on with you?
What... all this.
- You're spinning out.
- Spinning out?
Yeah, you're gonna tell me you're not?
You're gonna tell me it's fine?
That you're all good,
then shut me out, go
jeopardize your job some more?
I don't know if it's Ray or Becca,
or if this all reminds you of your past,
but something's wrong.
I just want you to talk to me
and tell me how you're feeling
so I can help you.
So you can help?
What do you wanna know, Jay?
Why I'm crossing lines?
Why I'm fine with it?
Why I shut you out?
Why I shut down this morning?
No, that's not it at all.
But this is what you do.
Okay.
So then why don't you ask
the real question?
"What's wrong with me,
exactly how screwed up am I,
and at what point do you
cut your losses and run?"
Because that's what you wanna know, Jay.
I can't answer that.
- Where are we?
- Nowhere.
We ran every cell, tower, POD. Nothing.
Hermanez never left his property
except to go to the PO box.
I don't know where he took them.
Maybe they've been dead the whole
time we've been looking for them.
Best and worst lottery in the world:
Parents you get, kind of love you get.
Yeah.
You have to carry
the score around with you
for the rest of your life.
There's just something about this girl.
She took his hand.
She's just so...
Trapped in it.
He was walking to his shed.
Hermanez had his gun on him,
and he was walking to his shed.
Okay.
Can we get blueprints of the property?
- He buried them.
- What?
We never saw Hermanez leave his property
after the PO box
because he didn't have to.
Hermanez lives at the edge of
industrial land in Hegewisch.
His trailer is right where
a factory was.
Now the factory's gone,
but that whole area is filled
with underground storage tanks.
Hermanez has three of them
on his property.
Hermanez left, went to
the PO box, picked up the cash,
dropped it off, came back.
Jay and I were pulling up
as he was walking to his shed
with his gun.
He was on his way to kill them.
We just got there first.
They're still there.
Victims are a tender aged female
and an adult male.
We have credible intelligence
they're buried in this ground.
So we're conduct a grid,
we separate three feet apart
and search every inch of this property.
Address off of me.
Let's go.
Hold on.
I got something.
- I got an edge.
- You got an edge?
Yeah, here. Come on.
She's alive!
Get those paramedics over here now!
Father's DOA!
I gotcha, I gotcha.
Hi, sweetie. It's okay.
It's okay. I got you.
It's okay.
Hey, I'm Hailey.
It's okay, no one else
is gonna hurt you, okay?
I got you. I got you.
Okay?
- You're still here, huh?
- Yeah.
I'm guessing
for the same reason you are.
I'm waiting for Med to call,
give Becca the all clear.
Hmm.
She ID'd Hermanez.
She's lucid, calm.
Strong kid.
I was gonna get some coffee.
You want some?
Yeah.
You know, if I wasn't working with you
- and Jay...
- Mm.
I would've used ICE.
I know. Wouldn't have worked.
Hermanez never would've talked.
Yeah.
I would've crossed a line
only to have run out of time.
Wouldn't have figured out
where they were.
Would've just done it blindly
to break him.
- What does that say about me?
- Hmm.
- You want an honest answer?
- Wait, you got one?
He says you became a cop
because when you were a little kid,
your dad beat your mom, beat you.
You couldn't do anything about it 'cause
you were just a child.
He was bigger than you.
You don't know my family.
I know you.
My dad's not some villain
from a gothic novel.
I get that.
Hailey, you got a gun and a badge.
You're bigger now.
So every monster I see is my dad?
Are they?
Every hurt little kid is me?
What, am I unfit to be a cop?
If you're unfit, I'm unfit.
You're not the first person
to psychoanalyze me,
not even today.
I'm sure that's true.
Hey, you're good at this job...
For the same reasons you're bad at it.
You control yourself
miraculously well.
You were calm,
balanced, unemotional...
Till something touches
that bruised part of you...
And you lose all control.
I don't wanna be that way.
- I don't.
- I know.
And you can find a way not to be.
'Cause I think this way...
I really think this way's
gonna cost you.
You came.
You asked me to.
I don't think I ever really learned
how to do it properly.
Relationships, intimacy.
Telling people how I feel.
You couldn't do that in my house.
When I was a kid,
being told "I love you"
was always after "I'm sorry."
They were the same thing.
"I'm sorry I hurt you.
It won't happen again.
I love you."
And you know,
I believe it every time.
And they did love me,
but then a day later, a week later...
Maybe there's some part of me
that every time I hear "I love you,"
I'm just waiting for the punch.
For the "I'm sorry" that's gonna come.
Look, I don't know how to do this,
but I want to.
I want to so badly.
I wanna be with you,
I wanna learn to do this,
I want to be better.
Then we'll figure it out.
'Cause I wanna be with you too.
And I'm not going anywhere, Hailey.
Really, I'm not.
Jay, I do.
I love you so much.