- Moving here was the best
decision we ever made.
We can just drink
on the street.
- Here’s to going
hard all night long.
- Cheers.
[snoring]
- Okay, babe,
let’s get you home.
- Okay.
- What?
Did you forget to pay rent?
- Is it the first already?
- It’s the 15th.
[gasps]
[doors rattle]
- They changed the locks.
- Or they just locked the door.
You’re not using your key.
- You know what?
It’s cool.
Me and the landlord
are pretty tight.
Yeah, we’re chill.
We text like every day.
- This is just an ongoing thread
of her begging you to pay rent
and you responding with gifs.
She said this morning,
"This is your last warning.
Pay rent or you’re evicted,
you absolute shitshow."
You respond, "whoops, lol"
with a gif of Kelsey Grammer
falling off a stage.
God damn it, Emily!
- I thought we were
goofing around.
- Why?
- Well, looks like we’re going
apartment hunting tomorrow.
Better get a good
night’s sleep, right?
- On the sidewalk?
[snoring]
- Wow, you are a shitshow.
- This place is such a catch.
Amazing location,
close to the subway.
[rattling]
Upstairs from it, actually.
Very lively neighborhood.
[muffled shouting]
[gunshot]
[alarm blaring]
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
[rattling]
This one has a
totally retro kitchen.
And plumbing.
Whoa, neat.
[rattling]
- The neighbors are so friendly.
They just had twins.
[babies crying]
No surprise, because
they are always doing it.
[moaning]
- Already, Darren?
- It does not make me
less of a man.
- Whatever. This is the
nicest place we’ve seen.
We’ll take it.
[bell dings]
- Ah, I’m so sorry.
It just went off the market.
- Just now?
- Mm-hmm.
- While we were talking?
- I could put
in a counter offer,
but the other couple has offered
six months’ rent in advance.
What’s your credit score?
- Uh...
- A+.
[laughs]
- Get out.
- A+, Murph?
What were you thinking?
A- is much more believable.
- Thanks for coming!
- Moving day, Bee.
- After two weeks of dating,
you’re finally
moving in with me.
My friends call it
a mid-life crisis,
but my company is
going to solve aging,
so there’s no such
thing as mid-life.
- Whatever. You got rid of that
weird roommate, right?
- Oh, that was,
uh, that was my wife.
- Whoever she was,
she had an attitude.
- Well, she did catch us
in our marital bed.
Uh, can I get your bags?
- Oh, um, actually, real quick,
I just have, like,
a few more things.
[grunts]
- I assume you didn’t read
that copy of
the "Life-Changing Power of
Tidying Up" that I gave you.
- Yeah, but I got, like,
halfway through the title,
and I got, like, bored.
Like, why would
I throw things out?
Then I wouldn’t have things.
- Nuh-huh, sorry babe.
I don’t do clutter.
That’s one of
my ten tenets of success.
My ten-nets, if you will.
Some of this stuff’s got to go.
- But Brycie, we have to make
your home feel like our home.
How would you feel if you
left your fiancé of two months
to move in with your millionaire
boyfriend of two weeks?
You’d probably need, like,
a lot of pairs of shoes, right?
That’s like a really
brave thing to do.
- Shoes are fine, Bridget.
It’s this other stuff.
You got like a picnic
basket of hanging balls,
whatever those are.
- I mean, do we really need
an entire box
of Marilyn Monroe
coffee table books?
- Oh, yeah, I just like
super relate to her.
I like love all her quotes about
having an awful personality
and how people just like
have to deal with it.
- Yeah, I’m seeing
a lot of quotes in here.
Quotes on pillows.
Quotes on picture frames.
Big quotes built out
of many smaller quotes.
- Well, I’m sorry
if I’m deep, Bryce.
- Is that deep?
"This bitch needs wine"?
- Wine is deep.
They have it Europe.
- What is this shirt for?
- Oh, my God, Bryce.
For when this bitch needs wine.
Literally, it’s like
the only item of clothing
you don’t need explained.
- Do we need three boxes
full of candles?
- Oh, okay,
good question, Bryce.
Um, do we need the house to
smell like Tahitian vanilla?
Yes.
- Do you need a whole barrel
full of dream catchers?
- Oh, okay. So you would
just be like cool
if I just got like
killed by a spirit. Wow.
- There are no spirits in my
luxury smart home, Bridget.
It was built in 2017.
- Okay, yeah, and if you want
it to stay that way,
you’ll let me hang
that dream catcher,
light some incense, and do an
intention ritual with my coven.
What? It works.
I put a hex on my ex’s ex,
and she got pregnant.
Can you imagine?
Being fat?
- All right,
why don’t we start small.
We can throw out some of
these old Halloween costumes.
We’ve got sexy police officer.
- Not that one.
- Sexy firefighter.
- I...
- Sexy volunteer firefighter.
How is this different?
- Um, okay, I’ll just
like spell it out for you.
Like the fact
that they aren’t doing it
for money makes it sexier.
- But does it spark joy?
- Like my picture frame?
- No.
- I guess people really like--
- Put it in your hands, okay?
Really take a moment.
How does it make you feel?
- It makes me feel...
like if you threw it out,
I’d lose my shit.
I’m sorry.
Are you like trying
to get out of helping me move
because you’re like old?
- No.
- Because you’re acting
really old.
- 45 is the new 25.
I ran a half marathon
last month.
I eat acai bowls.
I take concentrated
yak musk supplements.
In 10 years, I’ll be ageless
and living on Mars.
- Whatever. It’s no big.
I’ll just like text my ex.
He’s a personal trainer.
He loves doing me favors
because he knows I’m like...
...super appreciative.
- That won’t be necessary.
Let me text
my personal assistant.
- So, it’s really
over then, huh?
- I guess so.
I can’t believe you’re leaving.
- Oh, uh, I thought
you were leaving.
- No, I thought
- Are you kidding me?
I’m not walking away from
this sweet apartment.
- Neither would I.
This is the best place
I’ve ever lived.
There’s a fucking clawfoot tub.
- Hannah, I can’t
let you be trapped
in this home that we shared.
Let this 2,000 square foot
rent-controlled apartment
be my burden to bear.
- So selfless, but Brennan,
after everything I did,
you should be the one to go out.
Meet new people.
Like a realtor.
He’ll help you find a new place.
- Just go, Hannah!
It hurts for me to see you here.
And take our memories with you.
They’re cheesy as fuck
and they ruin the décor.
[glass breaks]
- Oh, that’s fine.
I’m fine with that.
I’m okay with things being
a little out of place.
You’re the neat freak.
How will you deal with
the nasty wine stain on the rug?
- What wine stain?
- That wine stain.
- I can replace it.
- Ah!
- I cheated on you.
There, in the bedroom
we once shared.
- You sick bitch.
I’ll have to burn the mattress,
because I’m not leaving.
- It was actually on the floor.
Our passion was too great,
and we made love on this
gorgeous reclaimed
wood flooring.
God, I love these floors.
- You’re killing me, Hannah!
Because I hate talking
on the phone,
and now I’m going to have
to call the landlord
to get the floors refinished.
- That’s who I cheated
on you with.
Do you really want to write
a check every month
to the man who cuckolded you?
- Yeah, that’s fine.
I’ll write him a check.
- Get the fuck out of my
super-fucking cool apartment!
- I’m not leaving this
apartment! It’s too sick.
- The lease is in my name.
- My mom co-signed.
- Okay, fine.
We’re both adults.
We’ll just cohabitate until
one of us finds another place.
Or I bring a guy home and
make you so jealous
with our super-loud
lovemaking that you just leave
on your own accord.
- You’re not loud.
- Maybe not with you.
- This place is so big.
- $800 a month.
This old bag has no idea
what she’s got.
We love the place.
- Oh, thank you.
You know, my daughter
and son-in-law
bought their first home, so I
was feeling a little lonesome.
I don’t need the money.
Really, I don’t.
I’m just looking to take
in a sweet young couple
that would like to save up
for their first home.
- Aw, that’s so nice.
I shouldn’t have called
the old bag an old bag.
- We should jump on this
before someone else scoops it.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
- I’m Grant.
- I’m Jon.
- I hope you don’t mind
we brought flowers.
- Oh, isn’t that lovely?
- Oh, my goodness.
This place is beautiful.
The kitchen is gorgeous.
We love to cook.
- Ain’t that something?
So do I.
- We will have to trade recipes.
- Yes, we will.
Let me show you the rest
of the house.
And that’s Grant and--
- Jon.
- --Jon. Come on.
- This is great.
- Did he just stunt on me?
- Oh, my God, he stunted on you.
- I think this is
what stunting is.
- Well, it’s getting to be
this old bag’s bedtime.
I’ll review the applications
in the morning, my darlings.
- What did you put for
our current landlord?
- I put my brother’s number.
- Nice.
- Remind me to text
him a head’s up later.
- Angela, would you mind
if we took one more look
at your veranda?
- Yeah, we wanted to measure it
for our herb garden.
- Oh, an herb garden.
I used to have an herb garden.
Of course, come on.
Come on.
[chattering]
- We also had an herb garden.
- God damn it, they’re perfect.
Why did I waste my good cursive
on this application?
- Oh, it isn’t over yet.
I secretly photographed
their application.
Look, we have all their info.
Let’s go dig up some dirt.
- Oh, Brennan, you’re here.
Shoot, I just got back
with my romantic partner.
- Huh?
- I understand this must be
really hard for you to see.
I’ll try to be
as quiet as I can.
[moans]
- Wow, you’re evil.
- I totally understand if
this makes you wanna move out.
[moans]
- Nope, this is all okay.
So long as you don’t mind
sharing a bed with me.
Because I’m not going anywhere.
- Whoa, whoa, okay, okay.
So you told me you had an
exotic pet lizard to show me.
If there’s no ’zard,
then I’m out.
- This is harder
than I thought it’d be.
- Yeah. I can’t move on
while I still have feelings...
...for this apartment.
Should we give it another try?
- I can’t get past
all the damage I’ve done...
...to the living room.
I trashed it to piss you off,
but now I don’t want
to live here.
- Well, ha-ha.
You played yourself.
Because there’s still
a gorgeous open floor plan
under all this crap.
Ha-ha.
Wait, is there actual crap
in here somewhere?
It smells terrible.
[grunting]
- You need to tilt it, Bryce.
- Ah. Aaron, there you are, bud.
Bridget, this is my son Aaron.
Aaron, this is
the young hot woman
that I left your mother for
when my company went public.
- Cool. Whatever.
- Brycie, when
you said you had a son,
I assumed he was like, 12.
Sorry, so you’re like
young and rich?
- Yeah.
- Really appreciate you helping
out your dad there, bud.
- You said you’d give
me a thousand bucks.
Where’s my thousand bucks?
- A libertarian just
like his old man.
Bud, you mind grabbing
the other side of that?
- Wait!
This looks
like super heavy
and I’m pretty
worried about you.
So I should probably spot you.
Oh, my God, lats.
- Dad, your weird girlfriend
is getting in the way.
- Uh, Bridg, do you mind, babe?
- Oh, I’m sorry, Bryce.
Earlier you were like, "Oh,
babe, could you get me a water?
I’m feeling light headed."
And now suddenly
you don’t want my help?
Um, mucho apologies, Bryce,
but this bitch is independent.
Okay, everyone,
we’re lifting
on three, two, one.
Oh, my God, abs.
- Bridg.
- Oh, my God, Aaron, it’s like
fate that I ran into you.
Um, could you like
help me with this?
I think my tits are
getting in the way.
- Yeah, sure. Whatever.
- Thank you so much.
- All right,
I see what’s going on here.
Aaron, why don’t
you head home, bud?
I can take it from here.
- Whatever.
- Oh, my God, glutes.
- I’m a tech guy who ignores
the impoverished,
and uses his excessive wealth
to try to colonize Mars.
And even I couldn’t
stoop this low.
- Brycie, wait.
I wasn’t actually trying
to get with your...
- Son of a bitch!
- They gave the address
of a fast food joint?
- Okay, I’m getting
to the bottom of this.
- Paw Paw’s Po Boys.
How can we spice
up your evening?
- Those scam artists.
- We gotta tell the old bag.
- What are you doing here?
- We’re here to tell Angela
all about you, you frauds.
- No, you’re the frauds.
But just out of curiosity,
how do you know we’re frauds?
- We took a picture
of your application
and called your landlord.
- Hey, that’s our move.
- Well, we have proof.
And here it is.
- Oh, no, you got
the wrong number.
I’m not his landlord,
I’m his brother.
Although technically he doesn’t
even have a landlord,
because he just got evicted.
- Crazy thing is I did text him,
he just doesn’t
like me very much.
- Well, we got
some dirt on you, too.
Feast your ears on this.
♪ And when a hero comes along
Whoops, wrong voice memo.
I mean this.
- Paw Paw’s Po Boys.
How can we spice
up your evening?
- Bribing a fast food joint
to pretend to be your landlord.
That’s low...er than
bribing your brother.
- Jesus, we didn’t bribe anyone.
That is our landlord.
- We live above
Paw Paw’s Po Boy.
Why do you think
we’re so keen to move?
- Mm, because we smell
like fried seafood
and Cajun seasoning
all the time.
- That sounds...
[sniffs]
...delicious.
- Garlic, paprika,
spicy remoulade.
I’m a walking Po Boy-scented
Yankee candle.
- So lucky.
- The guy knows it’s
a shit-spot, too,
so he tries to sweeten
the deal
with free beignets
and jambalaya.
- Yeah, he gives us this big
container and says we can just
"fill it up at
the soda fountain."
As if we drink soda.
- Do they have Mr. Pibb?
- Ugh, yeah.
- Sometimes there are
kids parties there,
and the clowns will want to stay
after and hang out with us.
- So cool.
- One time the kitchen
was on fire,
and the owner paid us cash
not to say anything
to the insurance company.
- So awesome. That’s smart.
- That’s fraud.
- I’m pretty sure it’s a front.
They have Ukrainian guys
in suits going in and out
all day with duffel bags.
- So you like live
in the movie "Die Hard."
- We love "Die Hard."
- We love it.
- It was supposed to
be something temporary,
until we found
the perfect place.
- A place we could
save up for our first home.
- We’ll get there.
- You know, that’s really
beautiful stuff,
which is why I’m gonna
go ahead and just,
I’m gonna do it, okay.
You’re welcome.
- I don’t get it.
You just deleted a file that
says "Emily Sings Mariah."
- Damn it. Really?
It was a really good recording.
- You worked really hard
on that one.
- Oh, God.
Okay, all right, okay,
but I’m actually going
to do this though.
Slate’s clean.
- The apartment’s yours, guys.
- No.
- Really?
- Oh, my God.
- Oh my God.
- Oh, my God. Thank you.
- Wait!
Hey, um,
I just want to say that
I’m like really sorry
about what happened back there.
You know what?
Like, maybe I’m actually not.
Because maybe that’s
what I needed
to realize that...
...you spark joy.
- You read it.
- I, like, watched it, but yeah,
I didn’t have time to read it.
But look,
what we have is, like, real.
I’m like the hot Grimes
to your Elon Musk.
And sure, there will be,
like, young, hot guys with money
who, like, don’t
have weird facial hair.
But old, fugly guys like
you have even more money.
Plus, you have like stocks and
shit, so you won’t ever be poor.
- Oh, Bridget.
- Oh, Bryce.
- Real quick though, do you want
to finish moving me in?
It’s supposed to start raining,
and my crystals are
climate sensitive.
Murph? Is that you?
- Oh, my God.
Isn’t that your nightmare
ex-girlfriend?
- What are you doing
in my new neighborhood?
- Have fun with
the apartment, guys.
- Yeah, we’ll see you
at the housewarming.
- Bye.
- That is so weird.
That is my ex.
He’s just like never moved on.
Is he looking at me?
[horn honks]
- So, do you guys have
any exotic pets?
- No.
- Aww.
- Is the clown here tonight?
- Yeah, yeah.
Just be careful, ’cause that
guy likes to drink a lot.
- So cool.
- Awesome.
- Sounds awesome.
- He’s something.