[distant siren wailing]
[cell phone ringing]
- This is Leya.
- Hey. Yo, it's Salim.
[Leya] Uh... oh. Hey.
[Salim] So that guy at your office
gave me your number.
Is it weird that
I'm calling you like this?
It's a bit unexpected. That's all.
Yeah, I get it. I just wanted to ask
if you want to meet up again, or...
Hello? Come on. Why...
Why are you so quiet? What did I say?
Come on, I'll buy you dinner.
[Leya] Listen, I can't talk now.
I'm on my way to work.
But why don't... Here's what I'll do.
I'll give you a call back in a bit.
How's that? Sound good?
Oh, shoot. Of course.
Sorry, sorry. I had no idea.
Yeah, well, okay.
Call... Call me back later, yeah.
[Leya] I'll see when I have time.
Okay.
Yeah, sounds good. Cool.
- [Leya] Bye.
- [line disconnects, beeps]
[sniffles]
Fuck. What the hell was I thinking?
[indistinct chatter]
Yeah. Yeah, that's the one.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
What's up? This is Carl Fredricson.
- [Leya] Hi.
- Leya Wahby.
[Leya] Hey, so your phone...
Is it not working?
Uh... no.
Tell me why you haven't called then.
I know I've called you.
- You'll hear from me when I can.
- Why don't we skip the bullshit?
- I know exactly what you're trying to do.
- Okay. What would that be?
Yeah, well... Hey, do you know your pal's
screwing me, trying to steal my company?
- [Marcus] Really?
- Did you hear he's a conman?
That's exactly your goal.
You're wrong,
but I have a meeting, so...
- I'll give you a call about this.
- I'm gonna buy you out.
- Yes, I'm going to buy you out.
- [Marcus] Go ahead.
But the bond you owe me
expires pretty soon, so get on that too.
- Send me your bank number.
- [Marcus] I will.
Have a good one.
["Försent" by 1.Cuz & Greekazo playing]
[Ravy] This is how they want us to end up.
What is he leaving behind?
No kids.
Nothing.
What was the last thing he thought about?
What was the last thing he felt?
- Was he afraid?
- [sniffles]
[Ravy] We have to stick together now.
[tense music playing]
Wherever we go.
We all have to be packing.
We're gonna wipe them all out.
All of them.
The pain his mother's feeling,
we'll make sure
their mothers should feel it too.
Do you hear me, Salim?
We're gonna destroy them.
[tense music fading]
What if I don't have someone
to cosign the loan?
But you can't expect that all... [sighs]
Hm-mm.
Yes, I know it's hard to get a loan.
That's what I said.
Listen to me. I already called them.
Yeah, okay. Thanks a lot.
Stupid.
[doorbell rings]
- Go in. Mom!
- [mom] Hello.
[Leya] Hey! Sami, take your shoes off.
[door closes]
[Leya sighs]
Hey, Mommy.
- [mom] Hey, sweetheart.
- Hi.
- Sweetheart.
- How are you?
[mom] Oh, I'm fine.
Hey, Sami.
Hm! Oh! Missed you.
How are you?
[mom] Tell me.
[video game playing in background]
- Oh, it's just... [sighs]
- [mom] Come on.
Well, it's just my business is having
some money problems. That's all.
But it's okay. I'm fixing it.
- [mom] Money?
- Yeah.
- Wait here. Be right back.
- [Leya] Don't have a heart attack, okay?
Wait. [sighs]
- [Leya] Where are you going?
- [mom] Hold on a sec.
- No, Mom. No.
- [mom] Listen...
- No way.
- Listen. I kept these for you.
- [Leya] No way.
- Come on. You can take them.
- No way, Mama. I'm not taking these.
- [mom] Just take them. Take them.
Honey, I've been holding onto them
in case of an emergency.
Take them.
You could get 50,000 crowns.
- Mom, I can't. I can't take this.
- [mom] This is all I've got.
It's okay.
You should spend this
on something nice for yourself.
Thank you, but I will be fine.
Come. Come.
- [mom] Promise?
- Yes.
- [mom] Promise me.
- I'll be fine.
- [mom] Honey, promise me.
- I'll figure something out.
["Rom & Kush" by Stor playing]
[Nala] Hey... Hey, hey! Hey.
Come. Come on.
Get over here. Get over here right now.
Come on.
- I don't bite. Come on, dude.
- [Tim] Um...
- [man] Hey.
- Yo.
[man] You got the cash?
- Um...
- [man] Answer me.
- [Nala] It's a yes or no.
- No, I don't.
- Then we got a problem.
- We got a huge problem.
You three owe me 30 grand now.
Does that seem fair?
- I thought you said 20.
- The interest just went up, freckles.
Um, come on.
We can work something else out?
And what would that be?
We could help you out on something.
Do a job for you guys.
You, do a job?
For us?
[Tim] Yeah, I'll do anything you want.
[man] What would that be?
Anything we want, huh?
[Nala] Anything, huh.
Okay, I just had an idea.
You know that little liquor store
right by the old park there?
Hm-mm.
I want you guys
to go in there and trash it.
Everything. Use baseball bats.
Make it look like a robbery. Okay?
Wait. What?
We can't just trash an entire store.
[man] What do you mean
you can't trash a whole store?
- We'll do it.
- [man] You'd better do it.
And if anybody here rats on us
or does anything
that could get me in trouble...
[smacks lips]
[man] Yalla, let's roll.
What the hell's with kids these days, man?
When I was around their age, plus with me
being a girl, all that pressure on me...
I'm being too soft on those brats.
Come on, guys.
- [Tim] Come on!
- Hey, this feels wrong, dude.
[Tim] What do you mean?
We've gotta show them what we're made of.
I don't want people to think
I'm a fucking pussy. Do you?
Get the fuck out of there then.
Get lost!
[man] Hey! Hey!
[man] Hey, stop that!
Take it easy. Watch out!
[woman] What the hell are you doing?
Get out!
- What do you want?
- [Tim] Money!
- [woman] Stop!
- [man] Take it easy! Calm down!
[Tim] Give me money!
- [woman] There's a guy trying to rob us!
- [Tim] Give me everything in the register!
- [man] Get out!
- [Tim] Give me money!
[man] Drop it!
[shouting continues]
[woman shouting]
[tense music playing]
[siren wailing]
[officer 1] Stop!
- [officer 2] Stop! Police!
- [officer 1] Freeze!
[taser buzzing]
[buzzing]
- [officer 1] Didn't I tell you to stop?
- [officer 2] Stay down. I said, stay down!
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey.
- [Leya] Hey. Is this our room?
No. Come.
[Leya] Okay.
- [Leya] Is everyone here?
- [man] Yeah. We want to get started.
- [Leya] Hey.
- Yes.
[Tomas clears throat] Hey, Leya.
- Hey, Tomas.
- [Tomas] Hey.
Right now I'm over in Singapore
for a a board meeting,
so I won't be able
to stay on for very long.
Okay.
[Tomas] These beautiful people
are the Macking investment committee.
Hassan you've already met.
- Martin over there is our tech guy.
- Oh.
- Nice to meet you.
- And Li is in charge of the legal side.
[Leya] Hi. Nice to meet you.
Uh, for me, you know, it's important
that I don't invest in random companies.
You see, I always want
a win-win situation.
That means I always try
and embrace my companies.
Grab them and squeeze them dry while
making sure everybody walks away a winner.
- I get what you're saying.
- [Tomas] Great.
All right.
The Chinese guy's here. I'd better go.
- Leya?
- Yes.
- Lock this in. All right?
- You got it.
- [Tomas] Then we'll do business.
- Yes.
That's what I like to hear from you.
Knock 'em dead.
- Chip, chop, ping, pong.
- [Martin] Leya?
[Leya] Yeah?
I have a few thoughts
on your data integration here.
And the machine learning element
could definitely be better.
I don't think it has to be.
Oh, that's him. Oh, for fuck's sake.
- This guy here seems sharp. [laughs]
- Yeah, Vlad's a real star.
[Martin]
I'm giving my recommend to go ahead.
I wouldn't do that just yet.
We have a huge problem here.
- [Martin] What's wrong this time?
- Problem? What kind of problem?
There's absolutely no way
Tomas Storm is going to be part of this
with someone like Marcus Werner.
Oh, that.
I'm in the process of buying him out.
The deal has basically been worked out.
[tense music playing]
Come. We have to talk.
[Viktoria sighs]
"It's pretty much done?"
Are you kidding me?
I mean, listen, Viktoria.
What was I supposed to do?
You heard what she said.
Tomas won't get on board
as long as Marcus Werner's in the picture.
Yeah, chill out.
- Can you get Werner out?
- Of course.
- How?
- I'll buy him out.
For how much? One million crowns, or what?
One and a half million crowns.
- But I got this.
- I hope so.
[door closes]
[sighs]
- [woman] Thank you.
- [Said] No worries.
- [Leya] I need to talk to you.
- Sure.
- Did you pick? Just give me one minute.
- Yeah.
- My company needs a little bit of money.
- So does everybody these days.
But now I have a real investor. That guy,
Tomas Storm. You've heard of him.
- [Said] No.
- He's really great.
He won't help until I own the company.
That means I have to buy out
the other guy, the investor from earlier.
Right. Good.
That way, you'll be your own boss.
Oh, where is that box
for the pick-up order?
- [man] Here.
- Thanks.
I was wondering
if you'd loan me some money.
Loan you money?
Uh, yeah. Yeah. How much do you need?
- [Leya] How much do you have?
- A decent amount. How much?
But it will take a while.
It's in a Lebanese bank account.
Number 12 and number 38.
- That'll be 215 crowns.
- Said. Said!
- Why is he here?
- [Said] What?
He's a nice guy.
Come on! Then go over there
and give him your number.
What does he need my number for, huh?
Just go over there. Stop it.
Are you stalking me?
What?
I just got some lunch.
I didn't know you worked here.
Pff! Sure!
[Salim]
Okay, just chill for a second. Hold on.
A little.
A little, huh?
I was stalking you a little.
I wanted to see you again, okay?
Well, you found me.
[laughs softly]
[Sami] Mom.
[Leya] Sami, you can't be here.
Stay in the kitchen. Come on.
[Sami] But my game's not working.
[indistinct chatter]
[Leya] Said.
[Said] Yeah.
I'm gonna need
one and a half million crowns.
- One and a half million crowns?
- Ssh!
I won't be able to get you that.
Listen, I could get you, uh,
a hundred thousand crowns.
But you have that house in Lebanon.
The house is for my daughter, Leya.
I can't just...
[indistinct chatter]
Where's Sami? Sami?
[sighs]
[Sami] Here.
- [Salim] Okay.
- [Sami] That one.
- [Leya] I'm so sorry. Sami, come on...
- No, it's fine. He can stay if he wants.
- This one goes here.
- Come on. Sit down. Sit.
- [Sami] And that one...
- [Salim] He just came right over to me.
Now we're best friends forever.
Right, Sami?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
You're lucky. He doesn't like everybody.
- [Sami] Now it's done.
- You finished it? Wow!
- Then you can make it do this.
- Yeah?
I'm the kid whisperer.
[laughs]
[Salim] I used to watch
my little brothers and sisters in Syria.
That was tough.
[Sami] Then if you press this one,
you can change it to winter.
Sorry about how I acted
on the phone earlier,
but you were calling me
in the middle of a big work thing.
But I can't start dating. Not right now.
That's too bad.
I guess that means I'll have
to eat here to hang out with you.
At that point, I'll call the police
to report you for stalking.
[Salim] Why?
Then I'll report you right back.
For what?
For... I don't know.
Because you reported me.
[both laugh]
- [cell phone ringing]
- Now if you go here...
I have to take this.
What is it, bro?
What is it?
We found that little motherfucker Amir.
Dani's runner. Guy who popped Ari.
Meet us at Skärholmen central.
It's all set up. Get in, get out.
- Hello?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. What?
Yo, Salim, don't mess with me.
Get here now.
You're gonna finish this.
It's now or never.
Understand? This is it. Get to it.
Chill out, okay?
Yeah, all right. Coming.
Good.
[sighs] Fuck.
Leya, I'm heading out.
- Okay.
- [Salim] Thanks for a lovely date.
- It wasn't a date.
- [Salim] Well, it felt like a date to me.
Take care, bro, okay?
Give me a fist bump. See you.
[Nala] Hey, the snitch was right.
He's still in there with his girl
at the restaurant.
- You sure that's the guy that killed Ari?
- One hundred per cent, bro.
I'll fucking destroy him.
[Ravy] Okay, listen up.
You pop that boy right in his face
so even his mom can't ID the body.
I'll make it right. Plus, he knows us.
[man] Hey, give me a kiss.
Come on!
- [man laughs]
- [kissing]
[Salim breathing heavily]
[couple laughing]
Fuck!
- Did you get him?
- Fuck!
He's a piece of shit! I swear to God!
- Salim, what happened?
- I almost had the guy, he hopped in a car.
[tuts] Dude, are you serious?
I couldn't line up the shot.
How could you miss?
Just take the fucking shot! Are you dumb?
I said fuck him up,
not fuck the whole thing up, bro.
[Ravy] Come on.
What was that about?
I didn't have the shot.
I swear, man. And then the guy was gone.
What do you mean?
What do I mean? He hopped in some car
and was gone. What else could I do?
Who was he with?
He was alone.
[tense music playing]
[Salim] Bro...
Listen. Next time, he's dead.
Don't give up on me yet, bro.
Okay?
[tense music continues]
I didn't do anything.
You know, he jumped me.
[officer]
Well, that's not what they say happened.
Okay. So what do they say happened?
Well, that Tim here
came and tried to rob their store.
No, I didn't.
I went to buy a snack at the store,
that man yelled at me,
said I couldn't use a card
and that I was white trash.
Then he punched me, and I ran.
[game voice] Police are incoming...
[gunfire]
You don't believe me?
Hey, listen. Of course I believe you.
I know you.
I know that you would never ever
do anything like this.
But these are
very serious allegations here, bud.
[Tim] Yeah, but they aren't true.
Listen, Tim, I'll help.
You won't have to go through this alone.
When the cops asked me,
you didn't say anything.
[dad] What do you mean? What would I say?
Why are you such a pussy?
I guess you're a big wimp, huh?
No wonder Mom left your sorry ass.
[video game continues playing]
[controller clicking]
[cell phone ringing]
- This is Leya.
- Hi, this is Hassan.
Listen,
Tomas Storm wants to see you today.
[Leya] Okay. Um...
Tomas has some time later today.
You'll be back home by tonight.
Okay. Uh...
This is an opportunity you don't want
to pass up. I'll pick you up in an hour.
Hm-mm.
- Great. See you later.
- Okay, yes. Great.
You're fucking joking! That's...
Hey. Hey, listen.
Can you watch Sami today?
Okay.
Okay. Hope it's fine. Thanks anyway.
- Talk later.
- [Sami] Mom!
Fuck!
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, sweetheart. I'm at work.
Double shift today. I can't really talk.
[blows] Okay.
- Everything okay?
- Uh...
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
Okay, bye.
We'll talk later. Okay, love you. [sighs]
- [Sami] Mom!
- Yeah, okay. Mama's coming.
- One sec.
- [Sami] Mom, I'm hungry.
[doorbell rings]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
[doorbell rings]
[sighs] Oh, dammit!
- [Leya] Hey.
- Hey.
[Leya] Thanks for coming.
[Leya] I shouldn't be gone very long.
I'll be back sometime later tonight.
Where are you going?
[Leya] Uh...
Honestly, I don't know.
Um, this big investor called me,
and he might want to invest in my company.
So thanks for this.
I know it's last minute, so...
If you really want to date a single mom,
this is as sexy as it's gonna get.
Me and Sami will have fun.
- Hey, Sami.
- [Sami] Hey.
- [Salim] What's up?
- [Sami] Nothing.
[Salim] Good. Come on,
show me our handshake.
Oh!
- [Salim] Boom! What are you building?
- Just some stairs.
[Salim] Some stairs, huh?
Where are they gonna lead to?
[sighs] Doesn't matter. Just some stairs.
[Leya] Here's his iPad.
- Mom has to go to work now.
- Hm-mm.
You already know Salim.
You guys get to hang out. Isn't that cool?
Yeah, it's gonna be really fun.
Give me some sugar.
See you soon.
[Sami] You go here.
That's right. There's drinks, um...
There's some drinks in the fridge
if you guys want.
And he loves pizza. Hawaiian pizza.
If you want to score a few points,
you could get him
a Hawaiian pizza or something.
[Salim] Absolutely.
Thanks for doing this for me.
It means a lot.
Good luck.
- Later, Sami.
- [Sami] Bye, Mom.
[Salim] Want to watch something?
[traffic hums]
[helicopter overhead]
Put your seat belt on.
- Where are we going?
- We're going to see Tomas.
Right now he's at a silent retreat,
but he wants to talk to you.
[atmospheric music playing]
[Sami humming]
[continues humming]
[Salim] Well, where could he be?
Maybe he's inside the oven?
No!
[Sami humming]
[Salim]
I think he might be in the bathroom.
Yeah, I'll just go check
the bathroom then.
Ay! [laughs] Hey!
- [Salim] Where's the ball?
- There it is!
- [Salim] Okay, grab it. [laughs]
- [Sami laughs]
[Salim] Take it, then.
Okay, here's a question.
- Ronaldo or Messi?
- [Sami] Messi.
No, man. Ronaldo!
- No, Messi!
- Have you seen Ronaldo's free kicks?
- [Sami laughs] Like this?
- [Salim] Not that wide. A little bit less.
There. That's perfect. Stand over here.
Okay, listen.
I'll throw the ball,
and whoever catches it first, wins.
- Ready?
- Hm-mm.
[Salim] Okay, let's go!
Go long! Get it! Go! Go! Go!
Oh, man! You're so fast!
Wow, you're too good at this, man.
- [Sami] These bushes have thorns in them.
- [Salim] They've got thorns, huh?
- [breathes heavily] Sami?
- [Sami] Yeah?
All right. Come back.
Hey, come back here. Sami, come.
- [Sami] Hm-mm.
- [Salim] Come. Hurry up. Leave the ball.
Here. Come on. Take my hand.
Come on. Yalla, yalla.
We've got to go home, okay?
- Is that okay?
- [Sami] Yes.
Dani.
I've got that fucking asshole Salim here.
- I'll race you home now. Are you ready?
- [Sami] Yeah.
[Salim] Okay. Go, go, go, go, go!
You're so fast!
[Salim panting]
This way. Come on. Run!
Hurry, Sami.
[tense music playing]
- Are you good to walk?
- Hm-mm.
[Salim] Go, go, go!
Jump. Hold my hand.
Hold my hand. Hold my hand.
[both panting]
Come on. Keep up!
Come.
[Sami groans]
[Salim] Got you.
- Hey. Listen, mate...
- Hey. Welcome.
- [man] What can I get you?
- We need a favor.
Tell me what you need.
[engine revving]
[man] Are you guys ready?
[ominous music playing]
Go upstairs and check there.
Hey, guys. Welcome.
- [man] Where did he go?
- [shopkeeper] Who?
[man] The guy who just came in here.
He just passed through.
Do you want to order?
You hear something there?
I don't think so.
[man 2] Hey, yo! There's a back door here!
That piece of shit!
[man 2] I'll check the alley.
[man 3]
Don't worry. We'll get that bitch.
[music playing over speakers]
[Salim] Found you!
[panting]
- Was that fun?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Okay.
Ready to go home?
- [Sami] Hm-mm.
- [Salim] Yeah.
- Thank you, brother.
- No problem.
- Be careful out there.
- Thanks.
- [Leya] Hi.
- Hi.
What are you doing?
Well, this is a silent retreat which means
I'm not speaking even when I'm alone.
- [Leya] Okay. How's that going?
- It's going all right.
Right now there's a meditation.
Then we have a break where we drink tea.
Now, then.
They're telling me you need
eight million crowns to break even.
[Leya] Yeah, but that's still
excluding marketing expenses.
[Tomas] Hm.
Why don't we make it 25?
So that way,
you can really hit the ground running.
[Leya] Uh...
Twenty-five million crowns?
- Uh, yeah, I'll hit the ground running.
- [Tomas] Glad to hear it.
So, I want us to go live on Macking
in six months.
Sure. That means there'll be a few numbers
to crunch, but that won't be a problem.
I want a perfect stock market launch.
So, then it is true?
You're planning an IPO?
[Tomas] It's a done deal,
but it's not quite official yet.
But do you think you'd like
to be a part of this adventure?
[Leya] Yeah. Are you kidding? Of course.
- So, you're with me?
- [Leya] Yeah.
[Tomas] Hm.
Make sure you get rid of that loser
Werner, or else I'm out of the picture.
- Yeah.
- [Tomas] Can you do that?
Yes. I'm buying him out now.
[Tomas] Good.
I'm staying quiet!
Really glad you could come!
[Nala] What's up, guys?
Come. We need to speak. Come on.
With who?
[Nala] Tsk! "Who"?
That homeboy behind you.
Nah, you, dog.
Yalla. Get moving, kid.
Hop in.
- Want a drink?
- [Tim] No, thanks.
- You sure?
- [pops can]
[Nala sighs]
[Nala] So, then... did you trash that store?
Yeah.
- [Nala snickers]
- [man laughs]
- [man] You fucking did it, bro.
- [Nala laughing] Hey, man.
- Oh, my God!
- Well...
[Nala] Hey, we were just messing with you.
[man laughing]
- [man] That's fuckin' insane, bro.
- Should have seen your face! Oh, my God!
- [man] Yeah, that's right.
- [Nala] I'm glad. You did good.
- That cocksucker deserved it.
- [man] But the cops caught you?
[Tim] Yeah.
- You say anything?
- No, I didn't say anything.
- [man] Are you sure?
- Yeah, not a word. I swear.
Good, man.
[Nala] You still owe us money,
so you're gonna make a delivery.
Here. Take this metro card.
[man] Here.
[Nala] I'll text you the address
and the door code.
You just get in and out.
No stalling. You don't want to stay.
In and out like Snapchat.
You're there and gone.
[Tim] Hm-mm.
For sure. What's in the bags?
[Nala scoffs] If you don't know that,
you gotta be dumb.
I don't know what to say.
[boy] What?
[door buzzes]
[doorbell rings]
[unzips bag]
[door opens]
[thumping music playing]
[woman] Thanks you. Here you go.
[Tim] Thanks.
[Nala] She thinks I give a shit.
Let's see. Damn.
Hey. Hey. How you doing?
Are you daydreaming, dude? Money!
Oh. Yeah, here.
All right. That means we're cool.
[man] What are you waiting for? Get lost.
Um, what if I helped you again?
Then I'd make some more dough?
[man laughs]
Do your folks not pay your allowance?
Yeah, but I want more cash.
- [man] He's a a fucking Swede, dog.
- Bro.
That's the point. He's a white kid.
The cops won't look twice at him, bro.
I swear, this kid will make us money, fam.
Give him a burner. Listen.
Just keep it close, all right?
When it rings, always pick up, 24/7.
See ya.
[Salim] Oh.
- [Leya] Hey.
- Hey. I didn't see you come in.
[lighter clicks]
[Leya] I really appreciate you doing this.
That you would come here
to help me out.
I wouldn't leave my kid
with somebody that I really didn't trust.
I know it must have still
seemed like that.
You seem cool, I guess.
Thanks.
- Am I your new nanny, huh?
- [Leya chuckles]
- [Leya] I guess so.
- Nanny Salim.
Well, we got a Hawaiian pizza.
After that, we did some soccer for a bit.
Played hide and seek with him too.
- [Leya] Hide and seek? Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay. Who won that?
Me, of course.
- [laughs]
- He really needs to get better.
But I'll train him right.
I mean, he's a little boy.
- Yeah, but so what?
- [laughs]
[sighs]
[Salim] How did it go today?
I think it went fine.
- I talked to that investor, so...
- Oh.
But I'm still figuring out a few things.
Plus, I need one and a half million crowns
to buy out a previous investor,
and I have no idea how to get it.
[inhales sharply]
It'll all work out for you.
And money won't be an issue.
You know a lot of people with money,
don't you?
[scoffs]
Yeah, I guess, but...
They are the kind of people
who were born with money.
They're all pretty spoiled.
All right. I guess I should leave.
Yeah, I guess you'd better.
I have to get some sleep.
Thanks for another date.
- All right. See you later.
- Yeah, all right.
So, if you ever need someone
to babysit again, I'll be here anytime.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] What's your plan?
[Ravy] We wait for him outside.
I told you that from the start.
[Leya] Ravy.
[woman] Chill out, bro. Please.
- I have to talk to you.
- What's up?
- I need to borrow some money.
- How much money you need?
One and a half million crowns.
Clean?
- Clean.
- Two million dollars clean, Leya.
- When do you need it?
- Tomorrow.
And I get to see Sami?
Look, we're family, right?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Come by tomorrow. We'll sort it out.
["E.C." by Abidaz
feat. Chapee & C.U.P. playing]